

Banashankari Stage II Bengaluru, INDIA 560070 ▼ WHC9+8C BSK

% +91 97398 56528

డ్డి varungupta3009

Experience

Corporate Operations Engineer



Google Jan 2022 – Present (1 mo)

IT Resident

Aug 2021 - Jan 2022 (6 mo)

Global IT: Data and Reporting Analyst **Hewlett Packard Enterprise**

Feb 2021 - Jul 2021 (6 mos)

Student Lead in Network Security and Web Development

Developer Student Clubs • PES University

Jan 2019 - Sep 2020 (1 yr 9 mos)



Software Engineer

Mindtree

Jul 2019 - Feb 2020 (8 mos)

Education



PES University

Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science & Engineering 2017 - 2021



R. V. PU College

Pre-University, Affiliated to NCERT, New Delhi, Computer Science 2015 - 2017



Carmel School, Padmanabhanagar

ICSE, New Delhi — SSLC, Karnataka 2002 - 2015

Publications & Awards

Software Implementation of an Automatic Movable Road Barrier

IEEE, October 2019, ISBN: 978-1-7281-1576-4

Prof. C N R Rao Merit Scholarship

PES University, November 2019

Languages

English Hindi Kannada

Hobbies

Reading

Gaming

X Virtual Aviation

Music

Knowledge and Skills

Python 3 Experience Skill	
JavaScript Experience Skill	
C/C++ Experience Skill	
Windows 7/8 Experience Skill	3/10
Frontend De Experience Skill	sign and Development

Full-Stack	Web	Deve	lopn	nent

Experience Skill

Angular (TS), React (JS/TS)

Experience • Skill

WordPress, CMS

Experience Skill

Adobe Photoshop & Illustrator

Experience Skill

Adobe After Effects and Premiere Pro

Experience Skill

Blender, Pixar Renderman

Experience Skill

Cloud Architechture (GCP)

Experience Skill

About me

I am a programmer and experienced web-developer, fluent in Python, C++, C#, Go with over 9 years of experience in Python and C++, and moderately versed in 7 other languages. I am a polymath and love to explore and try new technologies and fiddling with anything related to computers or the Windows OS in general. I am also a graphics designer and a hobbyist hacker.

I recommend checking out my LinkedIn Profile for real-time accurate information, to stay regularly updated, and to get in touch with me instantly.

